-告诉他嘛… -对,就告诉他嘛
-Tell him. -Tell him.
-闭嘴. -告诉我什么?
-Shut up. -Tell me what?
你看你,连正眼看他都不肯
You won't look at him.
下回女人不看我时我就有新办法了
I could use another reason why women won't look at me.
好吧,好吧,昨晚我梦见
All right. All right. Last night,I had a dream...
我和你
...that you and I were
在这桌上做爱
Doing it on this table.
完美的梦中得分
Excellent dream score.
你怎会有这种梦?
Why would you dream that?
最重要的是
More importantly...
我棒吗?
...was I any good?
简直是棒极了
Well,you were pretty damn good.
真有意思,在我梦中我力不从心
Interesting. In my dreams,I'm surprisingly inadequate.
昨晚你在桌上表现神了
Last night,you seemed to know your way around the table.
真高兴能与你们分享
I love it when we share.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我不敢相信你会在她梦中做爱
I can't believe you two had sex in her dream.
抱歉,只有一次
Sorry,it was a one-time thing.
我醉得不醒人事,而且这是某人的潜意志
I was very drunk,and it was someone else's subconscious.
六人行 第1季 第22集 倒人胃口的约会
The One With The Ick Factor
你好呀,瑞秋
Hello,Rachel.
起来
Get off.
给我,你们能想像操作钻床的我吗?
Ooh,give me. Can you see me operating a drill press?
不知道,你当时穿什么?
I don't know. What are you wearing?
不知道,你为何想操作钻床?
Why would you want to?
只是暂时的工作,直到我找回部份的按摩客户
For short-term work. Till I get back my massage clients.
又是海盗?
Pirates again?
没那回事
No. Nothing like that.
我是个大笨蛋
I'm just such a dummy.
我教他们“自己在家动手做按摩” 结果他们真的就在家里做
I taught a "Massage Yourself at Home" workshop. And they are.
嗨,钱德,她可以为你工作
Hey,Chan,she could work for you.
谢了,乔伊,这是个好主意
Thanks,Joey. That's a good idea.
我可以,是什么工作?
I could. I could do it. What is it?
我秘书这几周无法来上班 她去动消乳手术
My secretary's gonna be out. She's having one of her boobs reduced.
一言难尽的波霸故事
It's a whole big boob story.
-我可以当个秘书 -我不知你是否是这块料
-I could be a secretary. -I don't know if it'd be your thing...
-因为这份工作得要白天尽量保持正常
... because it involves being normal for a large portion of the day.
我能办到
I could do that.
-那是什么? -我的新传呼机
-What's that? -My new beeper.
古生物学家要那玩意儿干嘛?
Why does a paleontologist need a beeper?
恐龙紧急事件?救命啊,快来,他们还是绝种了
Is it for dinosaur emergencies? Help. They're still extinct.
不,是为卡萝生产买的
It's for when Carol goes into labor.
她随时可以联络到我,她只需拨个号码55-吉姆宝
All she has to do is dial 55-JlMBO.
这号码真酷还能当孩子的名字
A cool number and a possible name for the kid.
-各位回头见了 -去见伊森小子?
-See you later. -Off to see young Ethan?
谢谢
Thank you.
伊森到底有多小?很小?
How young is young Ethan? Young?
年纪和我们差不多
He's our age.
当我们还是…
When we were....
-他是大学四年级学生. -大学?
-He's a senior in college. -College?
抢摇篮（老牛吃嫩草）
Rob that cradle.
他聪明,稳重和成熟
He's smart and mature and grown-up.
稳重和成熟,他是个大男孩
Mature and grown-up,he's a big boy.
这位小朋友不在乎你的年纪?
This man-child has no problem with how old you are?
当然不在乎
No,of course not. It's not even an issue...
因为我告诉他我22岁
... because I said I was 22.
-你什么? -什么?
-You what? -What?
-我不像22岁? -25,26还说得过去
-Oh,I can't pass for 22? -Well,maybe 25,26.
-我今年26. -那就对拉
-I am 26. -There you go.
听见没?
Can you hear that?
拿起电话后就会停
That'll stop when you pick up the phone.
-我来. -好吧
-Oh,I'm on. -Okay.
宾先生办公室
Mr. Bing's office.
-抱歉,他正在开会. -我没在开会我在…
-Sorry,he's in a meeting. -I'm not in a meeting.
他知道这件事吗?
Will he know what this is in reference to?
他有你的号码?
And he has your number?
好,我会转告他的,再见
I'll see that he gets the message. Bye-bye.
罗斯打来问候的
Ross says hi.
真好玩.现在做什么?
This is so fun. What do we do now?
现在我得开始工作了
Well,now I actually have to get to work.
“可能吧”
"Most likely."
我出去一下
Okay,I'm gonna be out there.
好的,拜拜
All right. Bye-bye.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
你在干吗?
-Yes? -What you doing?
窗户擦好了,蜡烛点上了
Okay,windows are clean. Candles are lit.
皮带太紧,我得去换一条
BeIt's too tight. Gotta change.
鱼翻过了没? 没,因为我做的是意大利面
Did I turn the fish? Nope,because I made lasagna.
-我是否已失控? -一点点
-Am I out of control? -Just a touch.
我不懂.你们从他期中考试…
I don't understand. You've been dating this guy since...
…开始约会
... his midterms.
为什么,突然间你…
Why,all of a sudden,are you so...?
-我怎么了? -就在今夜?
-What? -Could tonight be the night?
我不知道,他是个好男孩
I don't know. He's a great guy...
我喜欢和他在一起,但是,很难说
...and I love being with him. But,you know...
事情会发生就是会发生,这种事无法事先计划好
...things happen when they happen. You don't plan these things.
-腿毛刮了没? -刮了
-So,did you shave your legs? -Yeah.
罗斯,你就别再折磨自己了 这只是一场梦
Would you let it go? It was just a dream.
不代表…
It doesn't mean
时候到了,宝宝要出世了
This is it. It's baby time!
放轻松…冷静点
All right,relax. Just relax. Be cool.
有人呼我
Yeah,hi. I was just beeped.
不,安卓不在这儿,今天已是第三次了
No,Andre is not here. Third time today.
对,我确定
Yes,I am sure.
没错,我不做那种服务
I do not perform those kind of services.
服务?
Services?
哦,服务?
Oh,services.
对,你要打的是55-扎姆宝（特大号）
Yeah,you want 55-JUMBO.
没错
That's right.
没错,有U的扎姆宝
That's right. JUMBO with a "U," sir.
不,先生,相信我你不会想要我的
You don't want me.
从他的号码看来,你看到我会大失所望
Judging by his number,I'd be a huge disappointment.
好吧,再见了
Alrighty,bye-bye.
第一天上班如何?
How was the first day?
太棒了,每个人都很棒
Excellent. Everyone was so,so nice.
瞧,认识穿我鞋子的人是值得的
It pays to know the man who wears my shoes.
就是我
Me.
-不,我没告诉任何人我认识你. -为什么?
-I didn't tell anyone I knew you. -Why?
因为,你知道的
Well,because,you know.
他们并不喜欢你
They don't like you.
-什么? -我以为你早知道
-What? -I thought you knew.
-谁不喜欢我? -每个人
-Who doesn't like me? -Everyone.
除了…
Except for....
不,每个人
No. Everyone.
-你说什么? -别难过
-What are you talking about? -Don't feel bad.
他们过去都很喜欢你
They used to like you a lot.
自从你升职后,他们感觉你是上司，大人物
But you got promoted,and now you're Mr. Boss Man. Mr. Big.
宾先生,大老板
Mr. Bing. Boss Man Bing.
-我简直无法相信. -他们甚至还模仿你
-I can't believe it. -Yeah. They even do you.
模仿我?
They "do" me?
对,比如这样
You know,like,okay:
报告要“何时”才能交来?
"Could that report be any later?"
-我没有那样. -你有的
-I don't sound like that. -Yeah,you do.
这山谷回荡着美妙的
"The hills are alive with the sound...
音乐
...of music."
我的烤饼,“我”的烤饼!
"My scone. My scone."
我没那样说话,这“不”是真的
I don't sound like that. That is so not true.
不是这样,不是这样
That is so not That is so not
这不…闭嘴
That Oh,shut up.
-不会吧. -告诉你,我到九岁时
-Did not. -Up until I was 9...
还以为枪口就是犯罪现场
... I thought "gunpoint" was a place where crimes happened.
-怎么会. -新闻老是报导犯罪事件
-How's that possible? -It's always on the news.
某人在枪口下
"A man is being held up at Gunpoint."
惊慌的观光客在枪口下
"Tourists are terrorized at Gunpoint."
我一直在想为何人总是要到那儿去
And I kept thinking,"Why do people continue to go there?"
我该走了
I should go.
-除非. -什么?
-Unless -What?
除非你要在这儿过夜
Unless you wanna stay over.
我反正要在这里过夜…不如
I mean,I'm going to. So....
我也很想
Yeah,I'd really like that.
在我们考虑留宿的事宜之前
Before we get into any staying-over stuff...
我有些事情必须告诉你
...there's something you should know.
这个就像,明天一早有课?
Is this,like,"I have an early class tomorrow"...
还是你与山羊秘密结婚了
...or "I'm secretly married to a goat"?
在这两者之间
Well,it's somewhere in between.
就严格的技术上而言,当然,我还没
You see,in a strictly technical sense,of course,I'm not....
我是说,我还没有
Well,I mean,I haven't ever....
伊森
Ethan?
你是个处男?
Are you a virgin?
如果你们这些孩子,现在这样称呼的话
If that's what you kids are calling it these days,then...
对,我是个处男
...yes,I am.
我是说,你确实是个很会接吻的家伙,我没想到
I mean,you're just such a good kisser I would never have known.
我在每一个级别都是优秀,我只是
Well,I've excelled at every level I've been to,I just....
我只是还没跟那个特别的人
I just haven't been to that particular one yet.
我一直在等待适合的人
I've kind of been waiting for the right person.
-真的? -真的
-Really? -Yeah.
你知道我是在指你吧?
You do know I was talking about you,right?
喔
Wow.
你一直喔个不停
You keep saying that.
书报杂志,电影上不断出现
You know,you read about it. You see it in the movies.
甚至在家里练习
Even when you practice it at home,man,oh,man...
这感觉实在没得此
...it is nothing like that.
听着
Listen,listen.
你说你有些困扰
You told me something that was really difficult for you.
如果你能坦白,我想我也能
And I figure if you can be honest,then I can too.
别告诉我刚才我的方法不对
Don't tell me I did it wrong.
不,那件事你没做错
Nothing wrong about that.
我说了
Here goes.
我不是22岁
I'm not 22.
我是25岁
I'm 25...
零13个月
...and 1 3 months.
我猜我们之间不会有任何改变
But I figure that shouldn't change anything.
年龄根本就不是距离,而且,我完全被你迷倒了
What does it matter how old we are? Basically,I'm nuts about you.
我们第一次接吻就知道了,你没有提到“Tic Tac”（香橙味口香糖）
I knew after the first time we kissed. You didn't mention the Tic Tac.
我只是觉得你有一种自然的体香
I just thought you were naturally minty.
听着
Listen...
在你坦承之际
...as long as we're telling stuff...
我也有话要说
... I have another one for you.
我比你所知的年纪还小
I'm a little younger than I said.
-你不是四年级? -我是四年级
-You're not a senior? -Oh,I'm a senior...
高中
...in high school.
我们错了
What we did was wrong.
我竟和一个在建国两百年国庆（1976年）都还没出生的男人做爱
I just had sex with someone who wasn't alive during the bicentennial.
我刚做爱了
I just had sex.
伊森,注意听,你为何不早告诉我
Ethan,focus. How could you not tell me?
-你也没告诉我你实际的年龄. -那不一样
-You never said your age. -It's different.
我的谎言不会使我们成为48个州的罪犯
My lie didn't make one of us a felon in 48 states.
-你到底在想什么? -我只是忙于
-What were you thinking? -I was too busy falling
-不要说. -爱上你
-Don't say it. -ln love with you.
-真的? -对不起
-Really? -Sorry.
好吧,下来吧
Well,fall out of it.
走吧,你不该来这儿的,你该在学校过夜的
You shouldn't be here. It's a school night.
天啊
Oh,God.
我就像是那种…
I'm like those women that you see...
专门勾引小帅哥的女人
...with shiny guys named Chad.
我成了琼考琳丝（作风随便的性感女星）
I'm Joan Collins.
谁?
Who?
好,安卓再45分钟就会到
Andre should be there in about 45 minutes.
是的,长官,和服很特别
Yes,sir,the kimonos are extra.
好吧,再见
Alrighty. Bye-bye.
这样省事多了
It's just easier that way.
-快,你已告诉我昨晚的梦 -不,忘了吧
-You told me about the last dream. -No. Forget it.
为什么?难道是梦中的我对你过于粗鲁
Why not? Was I doing something particularly saucy?
好吧
All right. Fine.
不仅仅你在场
You were not the only one there.
乔伊也在场
Joey was there too.
好的
All right.
那
Was there...
还有其他人吗?
...anybody else there?
真的?没有…
You sure? Nobody...
…蠢蠢欲动的家伙?
... handing out mints or anything?
没有,只有我们三个
No,it was just the three of us.
是你跟钱德之后
So was it you and Chandler...
再跟我,还是我们三个同时?
...then you and me,or you,me and Chandler?
-你知道吗? -什么?
-You know what? -What?
有几次…
There were times...
…甚至没有我
...when it wasn't even me.
真甜蜜,伙计们
That is so sweet,you guys.
莫妮卡,伊森又来电话了
Mon,Ethan called again.
-什么? -伊森又来电话了
-What? -Ethan called again.
-你不想再见到他了? -不想
-You're not seeing him anymore? -No.
对,有些事是无法勉强的
Sometimes,things don't work out.
这跟他需要假条才能离开体育课无关?
This has nothing to do with him needing a note to get out of gym?
我什么都没说,我发誓
I did not say anything. I swear.
-他只是顺口说的. -下回见到他时
-He stopped by. -Next time you talk to him...
能问《恐龙战队》中最强的是谁吗?
...could you ask him which one the strongest Power Ranger is?
我的生活简直是太多彩多姿了 可以换个话题吗?
Oh,my life is just so amusing. Can we drop it now?
对不起
Sorry.
墨菲时间到了（恐龙战队台词）
"It's morphin'time."
-暴龙! -剑龙!
-Stegosaurus. -Tyrannosaurus.
我得走了
I gotta go.
哇哦,脑充血
Head rush.
再一次我必须得走了
One more,and then I have to go.
酷
Cool.
你要上哪儿去?
Where you going?
我要和同事去参加生日会
A birthday party with some work people.
同事?没人跟我说?
Work people? Nobody told me.
我知道,他们中的一部分…
I know. That's part of the whole...
…不希望你大驾光临
...them-not-liking-you extravaganza.
一个月前他们是我朋友
A month ago,these people were my friends.
当上主管并不代表我会变
I'm in charge,but I'm not a different person.
那么说你今晚该来,和他们多相处 让他们知道你还是个大好人
Then come,hang out. Let them see what a great guy you still are.
-你真的认为我该去? -对,你该去
-You think I should? -I really do.
我们能不一起去吗
But could we not go together?
我不想成为邀请上司的家伙
I don't wanna be the geek who invited the boss.
-嗨,你怎么样? -是的
-Hey,you okay? -Yeah.
-这对他来说也并不容易. -我知道
-This can't be easy for him either. -I know.
也许他需要一些时间来度过这个
This may take some time for him to get over it...
但是,四点钟《布偶宝贝》就要开始了
... but,then at four,Muppet Babies is on.
更深点,深点,深点
Go deep. Deep. Deep.
对不起,雪莉
Sorry,Shelly.
看到没有,很开心?
See,with the fun?
昨晚真是太棒了
Last night was great.
卡拉0K,我和崔西合唱了首“乌木与象牙”
The karaoke thing? Tracy and I doing "Ebony and lvory."
你表现得很好,大家仍然取笑你
You were great. But they still made fun of you.
-什么? -你现在成了“管家婆”上司
-What? -Now you're Mr. Caring Boss.
“我加入你”上司
Mr. I'm-one-of-you Boss.
“称兄道弟”上司
Mr. I-wanna-be-your-buddy Boss Man Bing.
我更迷糊了
Then I don't get it.
钱德,你得面对现实
You know what? I think you just gotta face it.
你像个坐在大办公室里的人一样
You're the guy in the big office.
有权录取他们,也有权开除他们
You're the one that hires and fires them.
-他们说你是个好上司. -是吗?
-They say you're a great boss. -They do?
但是他们不再是你的朋友
But they're not your friends anymore.
-我只是想. -但你不能
-I just want -But you can't.
我只是想
But I just want
不是要去…
Are you gonna?
卡萝和我有了新系统,如果打911
Carol and I have a new system. If she punches in 9-1 -1...
就代表她将生产,否则我就根本不理会
...she's having a baby. Otherwise,I just ignore it.
安卓呢?
What about Andre?
早上他接到我表弟纳森的电话
He got a call from our cousin,Nathan.
老实说我知道太多内幕了
Frankly,it was a little more than I needed to know.
那也是我的开场白
That was gonna be my opener.
你们看过洗手间里的新干手机没?
Have you guys seen those new hand dryers in the bathroom?
-我以为那只是谣传.-千真万确
-I thought that was just a rumor. -True story.
我得和你谈谈
Look,I gotta tell you something.
我不是17岁,我这样说 你才会认为我可爱惹人怜
I'm not 1 7. I said that so you'd think I was vulnerable.
其实我今年30,我有老婆和工作,我是国会议员
I'm actually 30. I have a wife and a job. I'm your congressman.
莫妮卡,这太荒谬了,我们在一起很开心
This is ridiculous. We're great together.
我们聊天说笑做爱
We can talk,make each other laugh,and the sex....
我虽然经验不多,但一切是那么美
I have no frame of reference,but I thought that was great.
-的确是. -那么问题出在哪儿?
-lt was. -Then what's the problem?
伊森
Ethan,it's....
令人讨厌的
It's icky.
令人讨厌?
"lcky"?
因为如此你就想放弃?
You're actually gonna throw this away because it's "icky"?
我是不得已的,我希望情形不是这样
This isn't easy for me either. I wish things were different.
如果你年长几岁,我年轻几岁
If you were older or I was younger...
或是我们生活在圣经时代
...or we lived in biblical times...
-我就可以… -不要说
-... I could really -No,don't say it.
爱你
Love you.
-你的手还没干? -还是湿的
-Are your hands still wet? -Moist.
那就再去烘一次
Let's dry them again.
这些玛格丽特鸡尾酒能再“烈”一点吗?
Or,like,"Could these margaritas be any stronger?"
钱德
Hey,Chandler.
宾先生
Hello,Mr. Bing.
昨晚爱你的史提夫汪达
Loved your Stevie Wonder last night.
谢谢.有关周数字的事 九点“之”前请送到我办公室来
Thanks. About the weekly numbers,I'm gonna need them on my desk by 9:00.
-好的. -没问题
-Sure. -No problem.
总得给他们些话题嘛
You have to give them something.
刚刚是格斯顿,山托斯 留胡子的那个叫什么?
That was Gerston,Santos,and who's the other guy?
-派崔. -派崔,对
-Petrie. -Petrie. Right,okay.
这周末得有人
Well,some people are gonna be working...
…加班了
...this weekend.
真好
Oh,that's nice.
罗斯
Ross.
我在这里
I'm here.
你在?
You are?
我们在…
We were just....
什么?
What?
-这下可好,我有宝宝了 -什么?
-Great. Now I'm having a baby. -What?
我有宝宝了.我有一个
I'm having a baby. I'm having a
-电话,电话 -电话在哪儿?
-The phone,the phone. -I don't have the phone.
我受伤了
I'm hurt.
莫妮卡,快走各位快点,她要生了
Let's go. Come on,people. Woman in labor.
-罗斯,看这是什么 -留着付计程车钱吧
-Look what I got going. -Save it for the cab.
你在干什么?我们要去医院
We're going to a hospital.
我不能漂亮一点吗?那儿有医生
I can't look nice? There are doctors there.
-乔伊,别翻冰箱了 -好吧
-Joey,get out of the fridge. -All right.
-那是干吗的? -路上吃的
-What is that? -For the ride.
-比如坐车的时候 -留着吧
-Like in a cab -Save it.
-真讨厌 -莫妮卡,快
-Hating this. -Monica,come on. Let's go.
宝宝就要出世了
Baby coming.
我真不敢相信,我快当姑姑了
I can't believe I'm gonna be an aunt.
-我快有侄子了 -真感人,走吧
-I'll have a nephew. -That's nice. Get out.
好的,我来啦,我来啦
All right,I'm going. I'm going.
走吧,赶紧
Here we go. Come on.